## Syafiq Sallehin

Malaysia



syafiqsallehin1441@gmail.com



01137639437



linkedin.com/in/syafiq-sallehin-94399425b

## **Summary**

Sales associate for almost 2+ years of experience in retail environments. Have dealt with customer and provide honest service that ensure client happiness and positive feedback. Inspired to be a Programmer and have flexible job. Enthusiastic and eager to contribute to team success through hard work, attention to detail and excellent organizational skills, always inspired to improve own skills and self-motivate

## **Experience**



## **Shop Assistant**

League of Gamer

Feb 2018 - Jan 2021 (3 years)

I manage the daily chore by cleaning the shop and organize before opening and before closing the shop.

- \* Organize, Handle and manage an event for multiple game competition.
- \* Inspect & manage shop inventory and restock them if needed, checked incoming orders and organized new stock.
- \* Maximized safety and production levels by frequently cleaning and organizing work areas.
- \* Manage Opening and closing account.

## Н

### **Shop Assistant**

Jun 2017 - Jan 2018 (8 months)

Inspected final products to assess compliance with quality standards and established tolerances.

- \* Maximized safety and production levels by frequently cleaning and organizing work areas.
- \* Helped customers find merchandise and assisted with sizing and accessories.

#### **Education**



# Responsive Web Design Certificated 2021 - 2022



Diploma, Hospitality and Tourism 2011 - 2013

## **Skills**

closing • communication skills • competitive • css • event management • html • inventory management • javascript • management • microsoft excel